<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Brands on Cartgasm</title>
    <link>http://cartgasm.com/brands/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Brands on Cartgasm</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2017 15:22:31 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://cartgasm.com/brands/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Alpine Vapor</title>
      <link>http://cartgasm.com/brands/alpine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2017 15:22:31 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cartgasm.com/brands/alpine/</guid>
      <description>Our Mission The Alpine Vapor mission is to produce the purest, safest and most discreet cannabis products on the market. We pair cutting-edge distillation technology with beautiful and accessible design to serve the full spectrum of cannabis enthusiasts, from first-time patients to experienced connoisseurs. We want to raise the bar for cannabis-infused goods and provide the world with An Elevated Experience™.
Our Method Pure oil starts with pure ingredients, which is why we exclusively use organic sun-grown cannabis from Humboldt County, right in the heart of California cannabis country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Honey Vape</title>
      <link>http://cartgasm.com/brands/honey-vape/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2017 14:02:57 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cartgasm.com/brands/honey-vape/</guid>
      <description>Honey Vape provides California Patients with the highest grade medicinal cannabis oil in the state. Our mission is to create the perfect blend of science and nature to keep our oils as close to the living plant as possible. We achieve this through our painstaiking cleaning and terpene profiling process, that produces the most robust, botanically identical, genetic strains so patients can enjoy their favorite strains in an oil form. Our system maintains the integrity of the flower by giving the patient back the original flavor, scent, and most importantly effect, of the the plant before it was even harvested.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>710 Kingpen</title>
      <link>http://cartgasm.com/brands/710-kingpen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2017 14:33:13 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cartgasm.com/brands/710-kingpen/</guid>
      <description>The 710 KingPen is LoudPack Extracts personal marijuana / THC vaporizer, or “Vape Pen”. This device has gained popularity in recent years, as tobacco products take on a similar look-and-feel with their version of the vape pen called, E-Cigs, and the stigma associated with marijuana use, continues to go up in smoke. Vaping has gained such widespread acceptance worldwide, that the word “vape” was recently added to the Oxford English Dictionary, as well as being named their 2014 Word of the Year.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>