<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cartgasm</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Cartgasm</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>(c) 2015 yourname.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2017 15:22:31 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Alpine</title>
      <link>/brands/alpine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2017 15:22:31 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/brands/alpine/</guid>
      <description>The Alpine Mission The Alpine Vapor mission is to produce the purest, safest and most discreet cannabis products on the market. We pair cutting-edge distillation technology with beautiful and accessible design to serve the full spectrum of cannabis enthusiasts, from first-time patients to experienced connoisseurs. We want to raise the bar for cannabis-infused goods and provide the world with An Elevated Experience™.
Our Method Pure oil starts with pure ingredients, which is why we exclusively use organic sun-grown cannabis from Humboldt County, right in the heart of California cannabis country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brass Knuckles</title>
      <link>/brands/brass-knuckles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2017 14:32:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/brands/brass-knuckles/</guid>
      <description>Knuckle up!
When it comes to Super Premium CO2 oil products, Brass Knuckles reigns supreme. Renowned for their fire grams and oil cartridges that are known for flavor and potency, Brass Knuckles delivers when it comes to providing consumers top shelf product and ending prohibition. Real purity. Real integrity. No nonsense. No bullshit. Whether it&amp;rsquo;s concentrates, cartridges, or batteries, one thing is absolutely clear: Brass Knuckles ain’t fucking around.
Brass Knuckles speaks to true concentrate connoisseurs by mastering the art of extraction, exclusively using top-shelf cannabis strains.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bloom Farms</title>
      <link>/brands/bloom-farms/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2017 01:46:39 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/brands/bloom-farms/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>710 Kingpen</title>
      <link>/brands/710-kingpen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2017 14:33:13 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/brands/710-kingpen/</guid>
      <description>The 710 KingPen is LoudPack Extracts personal marijuana / THC vaporizer, or “Vape Pen”. This device has gained popularity in recent years, as tobacco products take on a similar look-and-feel with their version of the vape pen called, E-Cigs, and the stigma associated with marijuana use, continues to go up in smoke. Vaping has gained such widespread acceptance worldwide, that the word “vape” was recently added to the Oxford English Dictionary, as well as being named their 2014 Word of the Year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heavy Hitters</title>
      <link>/brands/heavy-hitters/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2017 16:03:36 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/brands/heavy-hitters/</guid>
      <description>Our Mission:
A trailblazer’s companion.
Heavy Hitters, also known as “A Trailblazer&amp;rsquo;s Companion,” offers some of the most potent, high-end concentrates and vape cartridges on the market. Proudly lining the shelves of dispensaries across Southern California, Heavy Hitters’ cutting-edge cannabis line pushes the boundaries of the marijuana industry, continually inventing and innovating new processes to provide consumers alternatives to traditional smoking. They proudly stand as one of the first high-potency concentrate cartridges in Los Angeles, and true to their name, Heavy Hitters’ waxes and cartridges pack a potent punch that delivers all the wonders of a high-quality cannabis experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bloom Brand</title>
      <link>/brands/bloom-brand/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2017 01:46:46 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/brands/bloom-brand/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eureka Vapor</title>
      <link>/brands/eureka-vapor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2017 01:43:26 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/brands/eureka-vapor/</guid>
      <description>asdf</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vvs Pens</title>
      <link>/brands/vvs-pens/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2017 16:05:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/brands/vvs-pens/</guid>
      <description>Nothing beats being able to smoke almost anywhere and travel with technological elegance. Discreet. Smooth. Potent. Ultra Premium, Styled in different metallics platinum and variation of gold with the strain you want and need. There is an overwhelming demand for #VVSPENS. The Vaporizer game deserved a much needed premium/luxury device. VVS pens will soon be all over the state of California. Later in Colorado, Washington and Oregon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jetty Extracts</title>
      <link>/brands/jetty-extracts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2017 01:42:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/brands/jetty-extracts/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hmbldt</title>
      <link>/brands/hmbldt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2017 01:42:30 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/brands/hmbldt/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Orchid Essentials</title>
      <link>/brands/orchid-essentials/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 22:48:17 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/brands/orchid-essentials/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evolab</title>
      <link>/brands/evolab/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2017 01:43:09 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/brands/evolab/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Levelblends</title>
      <link>/brands/levelblends/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2017 01:42:56 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/brands/levelblends/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goldrop</title>
      <link>/brands/goldrop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2017 01:47:32 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/brands/goldrop/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>710 KingPen featured in Newsweek</title>
      <link>/post/710kingpen-newsweek/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2017 22:06:50 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/710kingpen-newsweek/</guid>
      <description>Newsweek unveils their latest Special Edition publictation entitled &amp;ldquo;Weed&amp;rdquo;. Profiling a the industry as a whole and spotlighting on few award-winning cannabis brands &amp;amp; products.
Lorem markdownum puppe hoc, te mutatus fretaque. Quos auratum acceptas satisque, aurum illum teneas: que auras lactis manu. Aevi longo portabant mater coniunx relinquite lunae, pectus omnia. Si efficiet lunae coniunx stillabant rore hausta Notum quoque caedis aevum. Uti petitve.
 Onerata destituit et faciem aeternum ferrum traxisse Parum cute arces Etiam populo quoque Ingenio animans denique agitat vidi horror omnem Quae forti atque Vitae paulatim te ego nullaque Neptunia maritum  Inplevere auget, spectatrix iurare novitate solent sumptoque taedas, triplices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test5</title>
      <link>/post/test5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2017 22:06:50 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/test5/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test4</title>
      <link>/post/test4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2017 22:06:46 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/test4/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test3</title>
      <link>/post/test3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2017 22:06:44 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/test3/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test2</title>
      <link>/post/test2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2017 22:06:40 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/test2/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>/post/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2017 21:49:30 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/hello-world/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>