<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cartgasm</title>
    <link>http://cartgasm.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Cartgasm</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>(c) 2015 yourname.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2017 15:22:31 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://cartgasm.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Alpine Vapor</title>
      <link>http://cartgasm.com/brands/alpine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2017 15:22:31 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cartgasm.com/brands/alpine/</guid>
      <description>Our Mission The Alpine Vapor mission is to produce the purest, safest and most discreet cannabis products on the market. We pair cutting-edge distillation technology with beautiful and accessible design to serve the full spectrum of cannabis enthusiasts, from first-time patients to experienced connoisseurs. We want to raise the bar for cannabis-infused goods and provide the world with An Elevated Experience™.
Our Method Pure oil starts with pure ingredients, which is why we exclusively use organic sun-grown cannabis from Humboldt County, right in the heart of California cannabis country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Honey Vape</title>
      <link>http://cartgasm.com/brands/honey-vape/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2017 14:02:57 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cartgasm.com/brands/honey-vape/</guid>
      <description>Honey Vape provides California Patients with the highest grade medicinal cannabis oil in the state. Our mission is to create the perfect blend of science and nature to keep our oils as close to the living plant as possible. We achieve this through our painstaiking cleaning and terpene profiling process, that produces the most robust, botanically identical, genetic strains so patients can enjoy their favorite strains in an oil form. Our system maintains the integrity of the flower by giving the patient back the original flavor, scent, and most importantly effect, of the the plant before it was even harvested.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brass Knuckles</title>
      <link>http://cartgasm.com/brands/brass-knuckles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2017 14:32:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cartgasm.com/brands/brass-knuckles/</guid>
      <description>Knuckle up!
When it comes to Super Premium CO2 oil products, Brass Knuckles reigns supreme. Renowned for their fire grams and oil cartridges that are known for flavor and potency, Brass Knuckles delivers when it comes to providing consumers top shelf product and ending prohibition. Real purity. Real integrity. No nonsense. No bullshit. Whether it&amp;rsquo;s concentrates, cartridges, or batteries, one thing is absolutely clear: Brass Knuckles ain’t fucking around.
Brass Knuckles speaks to true concentrate connoisseurs by mastering the art of extraction, exclusively using top-shelf cannabis strains.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>710 Kingpen</title>
      <link>http://cartgasm.com/brands/710-kingpen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2017 14:33:13 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cartgasm.com/brands/710-kingpen/</guid>
      <description>The 710 KingPen is LoudPack Extracts personal marijuana / THC vaporizer, or “Vape Pen”. This device has gained popularity in recent years, as tobacco products take on a similar look-and-feel with their version of the vape pen called, E-Cigs, and the stigma associated with marijuana use, continues to go up in smoke. Vaping has gained such widespread acceptance worldwide, that the word “vape” was recently added to the Oxford English Dictionary, as well as being named their 2014 Word of the Year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bloom Farms</title>
      <link>http://cartgasm.com/brands/bloom-farms/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2017 01:46:39 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cartgasm.com/brands/bloom-farms/</guid>
      <description>Bloom Farms is built upon the belief that cannabis can enhance a healthy, fulfilling lifestyle. We aim to remove negative stigmas by inviting patients to take a fresh look at time-tested and lab-tested medicine.
For an ethereal experience, choose Bloom Farms. Bloom Farms crafts cannabis vapor pens, prerolls, and extractions to perfection. At the core of Bloom Farms is the belief that marijuana is a holistic tool given by nature to enhance a lifestyle of wellness and fulfillment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heavy Hitters</title>
      <link>http://cartgasm.com/brands/heavy-hitters/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2017 16:03:36 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cartgasm.com/brands/heavy-hitters/</guid>
      <description>A trailblazer’s companion.
Heavy Hitters, also known as “A Trailblazer&amp;rsquo;s Companion,” offers some of the most potent, high-end concentrates and vape cartridges on the market. Proudly lining the shelves of dispensaries across Southern California, Heavy Hitters’ cutting-edge cannabis line pushes the boundaries of the marijuana industry, continually inventing and innovating new processes to provide consumers alternatives to traditional smoking. They proudly stand as one of the first high-potency concentrate cartridges in Los Angeles, and true to their name, Heavy Hitters’ waxes and cartridges pack a potent punch that delivers all the wonders of a high-quality cannabis experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bloom Brand</title>
      <link>http://cartgasm.com/brands/bloom-brand/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2017 01:46:46 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cartgasm.com/brands/bloom-brand/</guid>
      <description>The Bloom Brand™ is the premier cannabis lifestyle brand. Born in Los Angeles, est. 2013. Currently available in California and Washington.
Bloom products are specifically designed to both complement and enhance your life. Bloom products include The Bloomvape cartridge, BloomOne disposable vaporizer, BloomExtract concentrate, BloomDrop applicator, and the BloomKit battery kit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rove</title>
      <link>http://cartgasm.com/brands/rove/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2017 14:36:45 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cartgasm.com/brands/rove/</guid>
      <description>Rove built the foundation of their company on honesty, simplicity, and transparency. Their mission is to provide customers with great tasting vape cartridges and reliable and dependable vape pens. Rove proudly stands opposed to the trend of exaggerated quality and misinformation within product test results. Rove wants their customers to know they have their best interests in mind with every single step they take. They strive for excellence and are dedicated to improvement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lllllove</title>
      <link>http://cartgasm.com/brands/lllllove/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2017 01:45:22 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cartgasm.com/brands/lllllove/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eureka Vapor</title>
      <link>http://cartgasm.com/brands/eureka-vapor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2017 01:43:26 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cartgasm.com/brands/eureka-vapor/</guid>
      <description>asdf</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vvs Pens</title>
      <link>http://cartgasm.com/brands/vvs-pens/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2017 16:05:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cartgasm.com/brands/vvs-pens/</guid>
      <description>Nothing beats being able to smoke almost anywhere and travel with technological elegance. Discreet. Smooth. Potent. Ultra Premium, Styled in different metallics platinum and variation of gold with the strain you want and need. There is an overwhelming demand for #VVSPENS. The Vaporizer game deserved a much needed premium/luxury device. VVS pens will soon be all over the state of California. Later in Colorado, Washington and Oregon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hmbldt</title>
      <link>http://cartgasm.com/brands/hmbldt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2017 01:42:30 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cartgasm.com/brands/hmbldt/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Orchid Essentials</title>
      <link>http://cartgasm.com/brands/orchid-essentials/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 22:48:17 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cartgasm.com/brands/orchid-essentials/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Lemon Tree</title>
      <link>http://cartgasm.com/brands/the-lemon-tree/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2017 14:28:39 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cartgasm.com/brands/the-lemon-tree/</guid>
      <description>When life give you Lemons
Lemon Tree, the legendary Strain, descends from the Santa Cruz mountains to delight connoisseurs far and wide. With a passion for both cannabis’ healing properties and the potential for a distinctly pleasurable experience, Lemon Tree is proud to stand at the forefront of the marijuana industry’s revolutionary emergence. When a person goes home with Lemon Tree in hand, they know they’re buying not only a product but an experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nameless Genetics</title>
      <link>http://cartgasm.com/brands/nameless-genetics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2017 14:10:17 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cartgasm.com/brands/nameless-genetics/</guid>
      <description>Our Mission:
We’re trying to heal the world.
Nameless Genetics is on a mission to redefine the world of high-end medical marijuana by offering only the highest quality flowers, concentrates, CBD products and solventless extracts around. They truly believe in their medicine and, with more than thirty-two cannabis awards under their belt for flower and concentrate excellence, the rest of the marijuana world does too. From their flagship flower strain, Mega Wellness OG (their exclusive version of OG Kush) to their decorated Live Resin concentrate, Nameless Genetics strives every single day to improve their processes and heal the world through exceptional cannabis products.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plume</title>
      <link>http://cartgasm.com/brands/plume-vape/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2017 14:30:30 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cartgasm.com/brands/plume-vape/</guid>
      <description>Mission:
Maximum draw with minimal effort
PLÜME offers high-quality vape pens that present marijuana users a dab-like experience; complete with terpenes from the original flowers infused into their cartridges. They are proud to offer a value driven cannabis product that lives up to their name, creating a plume of smoke after each exhale. PLÜME is excited to supply their state of the art marijuana products, manufactured with the utmost care and attention to detail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evolab</title>
      <link>http://cartgasm.com/brands/evolab/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2017 01:43:09 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cartgasm.com/brands/evolab/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kurvana</title>
      <link>http://cartgasm.com/brands/kurvana/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2017 14:26:36 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cartgasm.com/brands/kurvana/</guid>
      <description>Established in 2014, Kurvana provides uncompromising cannabis products to those who need it most. Success for Kurvana began when a small group of dedicated experts became frustrated by the lack of transparency, accountability, and professionalism in the cannabis industry. Instead, Kurvana sought to revolutionize the industry through creative engineering, scientific discovery, and manufacturing excellence.
Kurvana gathered an accomplished team led by Ph.D. scientists and engineers to create the best full-spectrum extract technically achievable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Levelblends</title>
      <link>http://cartgasm.com/brands/levelblends/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2017 01:42:56 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cartgasm.com/brands/levelblends/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goldrop</title>
      <link>http://cartgasm.com/brands/goldrop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2017 01:47:32 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cartgasm.com/brands/goldrop/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>710 KingPen Updates Cartridge Design</title>
      <link>http://cartgasm.com/post/710-kingpen-updates-cartridge-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 08:57:40 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cartgasm.com/post/710-kingpen-updates-cartridge-design/</guid>
      <description>New Bullet Design</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>710 KingPen featured in Newsweek</title>
      <link>http://cartgasm.com/post/710kingpen-newsweek/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2017 22:06:50 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cartgasm.com/post/710kingpen-newsweek/</guid>
      <description>Newsweek unveils their latest Special Edition publictation entitled &amp;ldquo;Weed&amp;rdquo;. Profiling a the industry as a whole and spotlighting on few award-winning cannabis brands &amp;amp; products.
Lorem markdownum puppe hoc, te mutatus fretaque. Quos auratum acceptas satisque, aurum illum teneas: que auras lactis manu. Aevi longo portabant mater coniunx relinquite lunae, pectus omnia. Si efficiet lunae coniunx stillabant rore hausta Notum quoque caedis aevum. Uti petitve.
 Onerata destituit et faciem aeternum ferrum traxisse Parum cute arces Etiam populo quoque Ingenio animans denique agitat vidi horror omnem Quae forti atque Vitae paulatim te ego nullaque Neptunia maritum  Inplevere auget, spectatrix iurare novitate solent sumptoque taedas, triplices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test5</title>
      <link>http://cartgasm.com/post/test5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2017 22:06:50 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cartgasm.com/post/test5/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test4</title>
      <link>http://cartgasm.com/post/test4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2017 22:06:46 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cartgasm.com/post/test4/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test3</title>
      <link>http://cartgasm.com/post/test3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2017 22:06:44 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cartgasm.com/post/test3/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test2</title>
      <link>http://cartgasm.com/post/test2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2017 22:06:40 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cartgasm.com/post/test2/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>http://cartgasm.com/post/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2017 21:49:30 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cartgasm.com/post/hello-world/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>